<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project:Labs</title>
    <link>https://labs.adamjordan.id/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Project:Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 13:44:52 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://labs.adamjordan.id/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Easy Problems of Consciousness</title>
      <link>https://labs.adamjordan.id/posts/the-easy-problems-of-consciousness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 13:44:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.adamjordan.id/posts/the-easy-problems-of-consciousness/</guid>
      <description>In Facing Up to the Problem of Consciousness (1955), the philosopher David Chalmers introduced the term “hard problem” of consciousness, in contrasts with the “easy problems”.
 The really hard problem of consciousness is the problem of experience. When we think and perceive there is a whir of information processing, but there is also a subjective aspect.
 The Hard Problem concerns about the explaining how it is that a physical system can have vivid experiences with seemingly intrinsic qualities (qualia).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://labs.adamjordan.id/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:23:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.adamjordan.id/about/</guid>
      <description>This blog will be used to write down various things regarding Project:Labs.
Project:Labs We define Labs as a research-centric entity with focus is in technological advancement. The ultimate goal of Labs is to enhance humanity&amp;rsquo;s life for the near future. This project is open and not limited to a specific technology, and may include various techniques from various fields of science, including but not limited to computing, mathematics, statistics, biology, physics, and philosophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Consciousness</title>
      <link>https://labs.adamjordan.id/posts/artificial-consciousness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 19:23:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.adamjordan.id/posts/artificial-consciousness/</guid>
      <description>This is a placeholder for the first post in this blog. This placeholder marks the starting point of one project: Artificial Consciousness.
Artificial consciousness (AC) is a field related to artificial intelligence and cognitive robotics. The aim of the theory of artificial consciousness is to &amp;ldquo;Define that which would have to be synthesized were consciousness to be found in an engineered artifact&amp;rdquo; (Aleksander 1995).
Artificial consciousness concepts are also pondered in the philosophy of artificial intelligence through questions about mind, consciousness, and mental states.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>https://labs.adamjordan.id/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://labs.adamjordan.id/archive/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>